{
    "subject": "resource/Don't_Raise_the_Bridge,_Lower_the_River",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/Max_Wilk",
    "human_readable": "Max Wilk wrote Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9682775735855103,
            "question": "Who wrote the book 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8201985955238342,
            "question": "What is the main message conveyed in 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8178490996360779,
            "question": "Is 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' a fictional or non-fictional book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7814475297927856,
            "question": "What kind of work is 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7568692564964294,
            "question": "How has 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' been received by critics and readers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7524381875991821,
            "question": "Who might be the target audience for 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7087140679359436,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6904809474945068,
            "question": "What are some key takeaways from reading 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5613507032394409,
            "question": "What is the title of the book written by Max Wilk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3589526116847992,
            "question": "Can you name any other books written by Max Wilk?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Max Wilk wrote Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3650_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the book written by Max Wilk?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3650_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key takeaways from reading 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3650_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3650_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3650_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Max Wilk writing a novel called \"Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River\", as well as a screenplay for a movie adaptation starring Jerry Lewis. This supports the triple that Max Wilk wrote the book."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Max Wilk is the author of the novel \"Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River,\" which is consistent with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}